Hello everyone!
I'm Nattai Kormi.
This is Natai Kormi!
Hello! Today is the day!
I'd like to share with you the quiz
I won in the quiz project
As a reward for winning the quiz project
Today, the three of us
I'd like to go strawberry picking with these three.
Yay!
Strawberries!
I've been looking forward to this day
I'm hungry.
How's Nanaka?
I've been moderate, Nanaka.
How many do you want to eat?
A hundred.
Three?
One person and 100 pieces?
One person can have 100.
Let's all try for 100.
Yay!
Let's go!
So, here we are at Sugo Farm, where Strawberry is going to use today!
Sugo Farm, where Ichigo is going to use today!
Yay!
Look at these strawberries!
As long as you can see them, they're strawberries!
Wow!
How many varieties are there?
From the back.
Pick one up.
Delicious berries
Koi Midori
Autumn Princess
Kaori no
Wow! So nice!
So many!
It looks like they'll let us taste some other things, too.
I think we're all going home with nothing but strawberries in our bellies today!
Do you remember how many strawberries are on the chart?
Oh, 100!
I'm kind of rusty.
No!
In a snore state.
Okay, you're with me.
Yes!
I'll spread it out.
I'll try my best to eat a hundred.
Don't strain yourself.
I've got your favorite condensed milk.
Really? That's great!
Let's eat them with condensed milk.
I'll eat it with condensed milk.
Wait, wait, wait!
Oh, my gosh!
It's so good!
I can't wait to eat it!
What? Isn't it too much?
Yeah! - Yeah! Oh, my God.
Sweet!
It's so sweet!
So juicy.
Hey!
Juicy!
I could eat a hundred of these.
I can do a hundred! Can you do it? Not at all.
I can do it.
It's like a strawberry.
Right?
Think of strawberries.
I put a watermelon hairpin on this pink part.
I put a watermelon hairpin that looks like a strawberry from a distance.
I was fooled.
You got cheated.
Scam, scam, scam.
It's a scam. It's a scam.
It's red.
I got it so good.
So good!Nice!
I got it!
You did it!
I want you to have the ring.
Bon appétit.
What's this? Benihoppe.
Benihappe.
Sweet!
It's from outside of Japan, isn't it?
I wish I could live here.
Sleeping.
What's that?
It's huge.
What is it?
Wait a minute.
Hidden...
I found it.
Your favorite delicious strawberry is in the back!
Ta-da!
What? This is too big!
Eeeee!
You're so loud!
It's huge!
Huh?
Ehhhh!
There you go.
Ha-ha-ha.
Let's eat.
Go get it.
Okay.
You like it?
Yeah!
How do you like big strawberries?
Yeah! Yeah!
Surprisingly sweet.
Oh, my God.
It's packed.
Yes! Delicious.
I can't wait for you guys to find these.
Check it out.
It's leaking.
This one's a little rounder.
What's this?
Tasty berries.
Hmmm...
Ha-ha-ha.
Mmm.
Mmm
Ha-ha-ha.
Hm-hm.
Mm-hmm.
iPhone roar
Cute!
And then...
Oh, my God!
What? What?
Next is KAI MINORI!
Kai is going to be the first one!
I just heard that it's a little heart-shaped.
So cute!
What's the name of this place? If you come here with someone you're interested in and eat a Kaiminori...
Clap! No need for words.
Hey...
Let's find the one with the most hearts.
All right.
Let's play.
Heart Championship.
Can I have one?
Yeah, go ahead.
Oh, it doesn't look like much of a heart.
But it is a heart.
That's from me.
Each one's a heart
The more you goThe more you go, the more...
I'll show you what I'm talking about
All right, let's do it.
Ta-da!
What?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Who has the most hearts?
Oh, you're all winners.
That's nice.
Each one of you had something different to say.
They're all so different.
Thank you.
That's what I'm talking about.
Bon appétit.
Ah.
Oh, my God.
I got a heart.
How's it coming?
Did you get it?
Yeah, I did.
I got some.
You know, in strawberries, they're not red, they're white.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
They're different.
Two more kinds.
Next...
Princess Autumn.
Princess Autumn
Yes, sir.
A strawberry with less acidity and more sweetness.
Look at this.
So long!
That's right.
It's very long.
It looks like it's enough for two more!
Kay's hands are so small
So small.
The size of the strawberry is amazing!
Bon appétit!
Yum!
You can drink it.
Oh, yeah! I just drank it.
Ha-ha-ha!
What? When?
I just had a drink.
I just had one.
How many have I had? Are you counting?
More than 10.
Um, maybe 12.
Um, maybe 10.
I don't count.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Next, Kaori no
Kaorino
Mildly acidic, refreshing and sweet.
Mmmm
I heard it smells good.
Seriously?
Yeah, but...
It smells good.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Oh, no.
Ahhh...
I've had it with the bees. I've had it with the bees.
Oh no! Watch out, watch out, watch out.
Scary.
That's great.
I'm so happy.
It's like having strawberry perfume.
Oh, my God.
It smells delicious.
Feel the scent.
Mmm!
Easy to eat!
This one's dark too, but it's like a jewel.
Which do you want to eat first?
Let's start with Hashiyura!
Bon appétit!Bon appétit!
The shape is like a strawberry, right?
I know exactly what you mean!
So sweet!
It's a new kind of sweetness!
I've never tasted anything like this before.
Oh, it's delicious!
This is a black tongue.
How do you say black?
It sucks you in.
It's like a deep, deep red.
Se-uh!
Mmm! Oh, yeah!
Wait, I love it!
I don't know,
Hey! It's delicious!
It's so sweet, it's like a grown-up's sweetness.
It's so good, I can't even finish it!
It's hard to describe!
It's really good.
Can I have another one?
I'll have another one.
I want to walk around with it on me.
It's the same in Spanish.
It's like a strawberry with everything you want in a strawberry.
It really is.
Yum!
You're so happy.
Yes! Look at this!
Ta-da!
Black strawberries and
and Hoshu Urala
and Hoshu Urala, which were prepared as souvenirs!
I didn't even take them home.
I managed to eat them right here in the restaurant!
Which one is your favorite?
The black chigo-chan.
We were so happy.
My heart and stomach.
I'm so happy!
My goal, I lost track of how many I ate.
I think the three of us together must have eaten about 100.
Yes, the three of us together must have eaten a hundred!
Next time, we should all come together.
That's right.
I want to go to Gari Gari with everyone.
If we all come together, we might run out of strawberries.
We might run out, but we'd appreciate it if you did it again.
How?
That's all. Strawberries...
They were delicious!
Bye bye.
Delicious berries
Yummy berries.
Bye bye bye, let's have delicious berries bye bye
Seino
Yummy berries
Bye bye bye